{"experimentVersion":"micro_debug","participantID":"test","participantAge":"test","participantGender":1,"confirmationCode":"0426019","participantFeedback":"","totalTrials":20,"dataRecordFrequency":0.03999999910593033,"restbreakDuration":5.0,"getReadyDuration":5.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":1,"trialListIndex":[1],"mapName":"InformationScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":2,"trialListIndex":[2],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":3,"trialListIndex":[3],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":4,"trialListIndex":[4],"mapName":"StartScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":5,"trialListIndex":[5],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":6,"trialListIndex":[6,7],"mapName":"Practice","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[6.5317535400390629,1.2429542541503907],"responseChoice":["","10"],"choiceCorrect":[false,false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[true,false],"FLAG_trialError":[true,false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false,false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false,false]},{"trialNumber":7,"trialListIndex":[8],"mapName":"GetReady","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[1.2429542541503907],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":8,"trialListIndex":[9],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":10.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.9780426025390625],"responseChoice":["1"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":9,"trialListIndex":[10],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":10.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[1.1089859008789063],"responseChoice":["1"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"1","trialQuestion":"How many taco-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"taco","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[]}]}